It will take what you love most.
Insidious: Chapter 2 is a horror, thriller film directed by James Wan.
The haunted Lambert family seeks to uncover the mysterious childhood secret
that has left them dangerously connected to the spirit world.
Josh Lambert, played by Patrick Wilson.
Renai Lambert, played by Rose Byrne.
Elise Rainier, played by Lin Shaye.
Dalton Lambert, played by Ty Simpkins.
Lorraine Lambert, played by Barbara Hershey.
Carl, played by Steve Coulter.
Insidious: Chapter 2 is a 2013 American supernatural
horror film directed by James Wan.
It is the sequel to Insidious (2010), and the second installment in the Insidious
franchise, and the fourth in terms of the series' in-story chronology.
The film stars Patrick Wilson and Rose Byrne, reprising their roles as Josh and Renai Lambert, a husband and
wife who seek to uncover the secret that has left them dangerously connected to the spirit world.
The film was released on September 13, 2013.
Two prequels, Chapter 3 and The Last Key were released on June 5, 2015, and January 5, 2018,
respectively, with a direct sequel to Chapter 2, The Red Door, released on July 7, 2023.
The film explores themes of haunted house, possession, demon, family, ghost.
The tone is dark and intense.